作词 : cAnON.
作曲 : 澤野　弘之
编曲 : 澤野弘之
Am I still in the glum nightmare?
我仍深陷在阴沉可怖的噩梦中吗？
Or am I mere stoned?
抑或只是神志不清？
Tiny bit of reason still remains in my right hand
我右手中仍残留有些许理智
That power of ache will just keep me alive
这痛楚的力量会让我坚持活下去
Can't touch nothing 'bout the world
我已感受不到这个世界一丝一毫
But the truth nothing almost has revealed
真相却全被深深雪藏
Then smash out the future told
随后未来被粉碎，我被告知
It's time to end these miseries
是时候来结束这些痛苦了
Latch off my vegus nerve
我的神经被紧锁
What color is my blood...Red, black or white?
流淌在我身上的血......它是红色、黑色还是白色的？
Now I'm getting ready
现在我已经全副武装
Oh, where are my frenemies?
然而我的枪到底应指向谁
If I got to lose control
如果我失去了理智
Will you kill me first?
你是否会先将我斩杀？
Deep rooted anger still remains in my right hand
愤怒在我的右手根深蒂固
That power of ache will just keep me alive
但我还是要依靠这痛苦的力量生存
...
Can't touch nothing 'bout the world
我已感受不到这个世界一丝一毫
But the truth almost has revealed
真相却全被深深雪藏
Then smash out the future told
随后未来被粉碎，我被告知
It's time to end these miseries
是时候来结束这些痛苦了
Latch off my vegus nerve
我的神经被紧锁
What color is my blood...Red, black or white?
流淌在我身上的血......它是红色、黑色还是白色的？
Now I'm getting ready
现在我已经全副武装
Oh, where are my frenemies?
然而我的枪到底应指向谁
...
Have I gone so mad?
我已经变得这么疯狂了吗？
The pain's through my blood
痛苦仍然在我的血液中穿梭啊
...
Can't touch nothing 'bout the world
我已感受不到这个世界一丝一毫
But the truth almost has revealed
真相却全被深深雪藏
Then smash out the future told
随后未来被粉碎，我被告知
It's time to end these miseries
是时候来结束这些痛苦了
Latch off my vegus nerve
我的神经被紧锁
What color is my blood...Red, black or white?
流淌在我身上的血......它是红色、黑色还是白色的？
Now I'm getting ready
现在我已经全副武装
Oh, where are my frenemies?
然而我的枪到底应指向谁